Any number can play. Any number can die.
The Last of Sheila is a crime, drama, mystery film directed by Herbert Ross.
A year after Sheila is killed in a hit-and-run, her multimillionaire husband invites a group of friends to spend a week on his
yacht playing a scavenger hunt-style mystery game—but the game turns out to be all too real and all too deadly.
Tom Parkman, played by Richard Benjamin.
Christine, played by Dyan Cannon.
Clinton Greene, played by James Coburn.
Lee Parkman, played by Joan Hackett.
Philip Dexter, played by James Mason.
Anthony Wood, played by Ian McShane.
The Last of Sheila is a 1973 American whodunnit mystery film directed and produced
by Herbert Ross and written by Anthony Perkins and Stephen Sondheim.
It stars Richard Benjamin, Dyan Cannon, James Coburn, Joan
Hackett, James Mason, Ian McShane, and Raquel Welch.
The film was released to positive reviews, and has
garnered a solid following over time.
The script by Perkins and Sondheim was later novelized by Alexander Edwards.
The film explores themes of mediterranean, southern
france, cruise, scavenger hunt, whodunit.
The tone is intense and emotional and mind_bending.